Penny, I..I don't understand
Penny，我..我不明白
Most girls are born..
大部分女孩是天生的..
but I was made
但我是人造的
I'm the world's first synthetic person capable of generating an Aura
我是世上第一個能產生元氣的人造人
I'm not real
我不是真人
Of course you are
你當然是真的
You think just because you got nuts and bolts instead of squishy guts makes you any less real than me?
你以為肚子裡只有螺絲釘而沒有柔軟的內臟就讓你比我更假了？
I don't..um..
我不是..呃..
You're taking this extraordinarily well
你居然如此淡定地接受了
You're not like those things we saw back there
你和之前在那兒看見的玩意兒不同
You've got a heart, and a soul, I can feel it
你有感情和靈魂，我能感覺
Oh! Ruby, you're the best friend anyone could have!
噢！Ruby，你是世上最棒的朋友！
Uhh, I can see why your father would want to protect such a delicate flower..
呃，我明白為啥你父親要保護你這纖♂弱的花朵了..
Oh, he is very sweet
噢，他很溫柔的
My father's the one that built me
我父親可是造我的人
I'm sure you would just love him
我肯定你會喜歡他
Wow..he built you all by himself?
哇噢..他一個人造的你？
Well, almost
嘛，大部分
He had some help from Mr.Ironwood
Ironwood先生幫了些忙
The general?
那個將軍？
Wait..
等等..
Is that why those soldiers were after you?
所以那些士兵們才追著你？
They like to protect me too!
他們也想保護我！
Pfft
噗
They don't think you can protect yourself?
他們不覺得你能保護自己？
They're not sure if I'm ready yet
他們不確定我有沒有準備好
One day, it will be my job to save the world
總有一天，將由我來拯救世界
But I still have a lot left to learn
但我還有很多需要學的
That's why my father let me come to the Vytal festival
所以我父親讓我來參加維特節
I want to see what it's like in the rest of the world
我想看看外面的世界是什麼樣子
And test myself in the tournament
還能在錦標賽裡檢測自己
Penny, what're you talking about?
Penny，你在說什麼啊？
Save the world from what? We're in a time of peace
世界怎麼了需要你拯救？現在是和平時期
That's not what Mr.Ironwood said
Ironwood先生可不是這樣說的
Check down here
來這邊找
You have to hide
你得躲起來
No! Penny! What're you doing?! You don't have to go with them! I can help you!
不！Penny！你要幹什麼？！你不用跟他們走！我能幫你！
It's okay, Ruby, they're not bad people
沒關係的，Ruby，他們不是壞人
I just don't want you to get in trouble
我只是不想給你添麻煩
Just promise me you won't tell anyone about my secret..okay?
你只要保證不把我的秘密說出去..好嗎？
I promise
我保證
There she is!
她在呢！
Salutations, officers!
此致敬禮，長官們！
Why were you running?
你幹嘛要跑？
And.. what happened to the other girl?
而且..另一個女孩怎麼了？
What girl?
什麼女孩？
I've been by myself all day
我一整天都是一個人
You shouldn't cause such a scene
你不該鬧出那一幕
Are you okay?
你沒事吧？
Just a scratch
擦傷而已
Penny..your father isn't going to be happy about this
Penny..你父親對此可不會高興
Please, just come with us
請和我們回去吧
Yes, sir
是，長官
Come on, my friend's right in here
來吧，我朋友就在裡面
Cool
帥掉渣
(>_<)
(>_<)
And where exactly is....here?
話說這到底是..哪裡？
Hurry, close the door! She's coming!
快點把門關上！她來了！
What're you two idiots doing?
你們兩個蠢貨在幹啥？
Junior! She's here, she's back..the one with her..
Junior！她來了，她回來了，還帶了一個..
Guess who's back!
猜猜誰回來了！
Yeah, so could you define 'friend' for me?
所以告訴我這是哪門子「朋友」？
Stop, stop! Nobody shoot
停，停！都不准開槍
Blondie! You're here
金髮妞！你來了
Why?
為啥？
You still owe me a drink
你還欠我喝一杯呢
Whoaa..what a women..
哇..這女人真是..
Sup
好呀
Hmph!
口亨！
Whatever
不理他
This is it
就是這裡
You sure?
你確定？
You know, I'm just gonna take your word for it
好吧，你的話我都信
New recruits, keep to the right
新人靠右邊站
I don't get it. If you believe what you're doing is right, why hide who you are?
我不懂，如果你們覺得自己的事業是正確的，為什麼要隱藏身份？
The masks are a symbol
這面具是個象徵
Humanity wanted to make monsters out of us, so we chose to don the face of the monsters
人類想把我們逼成怪獸，所以我們選擇了怪獸形象戴上
Grimm masks..
戮獸面具..
That's..kinda dark
真是陰暗..
So was the guy who started it
出這主意的人同樣陰暗
Always sunshine and rainbows with you
跟你一起真是歡樂
Thank you all for coming
感謝你們能來
for those of you who are joining us for the first time tonight
今晚第一次加入我們的各位
allow me to introduce a very special comrade of ours
請讓我給你們介紹一位很特殊的同志
I can assure you, he is the key to obtaining what we have fought for, for so long!
我可以擔保要達到我們長久以來奮鬥的目標，他是關鍵人物
Thank you, thank you
謝謝，謝謝
Please, hold your applause
好了，不用鼓掌了
What's a human doing here?!
一個人類怎麼在這兒？
I'm glad you asked, deery
問得好，鹿女
Now, I'll be the first to admit..
我應該是第一個承認..
Humans..are the worst
人類..真是最爛的
Case in point
比方說
So, I understand why you would love to see us all locked away, or, better yet..killed!
我很清楚你們為什麼想把我們鎖起來，或者乾脆..殺掉
But..
但是..
So is he going somewhere with this or..?
所以他到底想說什麼..？
I'd like to mention the fact that you and I all have a common enemy!
我想說一件事實：我們有著共同的敵人！
The ones in control, the people pulling the strings, the dirty, rotten humans that run our kingdoms
那些掌權者、幕後操縱者、腐敗骯髒的王國領導人
Yeah!
耶！
Government, military, even the schools
政府、軍隊，甚至包括學校
They're all to blame for your lot in life
都是你不幸生活的罪魁禍首
And they're all pests that need to be dealt with
他們是群害蟲，必須消滅掉
Fortunately..
幸運的是..
I'm the best exterminator around
我是最好的殺蟲專家
No offense to any rodents in the room
無意冒犯在場的齧齒動物
Uh..that's a big robot
呃..好大一個機器人
How did he get that?
他怎麼弄到手的？
As some of you may have heard, this right here..
你們大部分人可能聽說了，這個..
is Atlas's newest line of defense against all the scary things in the world
就是阿特拉斯對世界上所有可怕之物的最新防線
And thanks to my employer
多虧了我的僱主
we've managed to snag a few before they..uh, hit the shelves
我們在它們正式服役前搶到了幾台
Now, many of your brothers have already moved down to our new operations in the southeast
現在很多你們的弟兄已經去東南部執行我們新的行動了
If you'd rather stay within the city..
如果你寧願待在城裡..
that's fine..
沒問題..
But if you're truly ready to fight for what you believe in
但你若真想為自己的信念而戰
this is the arsenal I can provide you
我就給你們提供軍火
Any questions?
有問題嗎？
We should get out of here
我們該出去了
All new recruits, please come forward
所有新人，請上前來
Welp..
好吧..
I don't know
我不知道
How can you not know?
你怎麼會不知道？
I haven't talked to him
我沒跟他說過話了
I haven't even seen him since the night you first came in here
從你第一晚來這之後我就沒見過他了
He paid up front, I lent him my men
他付了全額，我借他人手
And none of them ever came back
然後他們一個都沒回來
So where did they go?
那他們人呢？
What kind of stupid question is that?
這問題蠢出境界了吧？
They never came back
他們再也沒回來過
Who is this guy?
這小子是誰？
Don't worry about him
別擔心他了
Worry about me if I don't find out what I want!
找不到想要的答案，你還是擔心我吧
I already told you everything
我已經全都告訴你了
Torchwick hired my boys, and I guess he wasn't happy with them
Torchwick借了我的人，我猜他對他們不滿意
which is something I can relate to!
這一點我還是能想到！
Come on, Neptune
走吧，Neptune
We get everything we need?
我們弄到需要的東西了？
Well, we got everything we can
唉，能弄到的都弄了
Hopefully the rest of the team is having better luck
希望隊裡其他人運氣更好點
What're we gonna do?!
我們該怎麼辦？
I'm thinking
我在想呢
He sees us..
他看見我們了
He can't see in the dark
黑暗中他看不見
Don't let them get away!
別讓他們跑了！
Sun! The window
Sun！窗戶
Stop them!
擋住他們！
So you wouldn't happen to have..oh, I don't know
你不會碰巧正好有..該怎麼說
some form of backup?!
某種支援吧！？
On it
正在召喚
Everyone! If you can hear me, we need back-
大伙！如果能聽見，我們需要支-
Help!
救命！
They've got a robot, and it's big, really big
他們弄了台機器人，好大，真的大
Oh, I am not missing this
我可不能錯過這個
That Torchwick guy's in it!
那個Torchwick在裡頭！
But not like, it didn't eat him, he's like controlling it or something!
不過他不是被吃掉，貌似他在操作還是啥！
Where are you guys?
你們在哪裡？
Hury!
快點！
I..think that was them
我覺得那是他們
Yeah, I got it
是啊，知道了
Whoa!
哇噢！
We've gotta slow it down
我們得讓它減速
Got it
瞭解
Hold on!
坐穩！
Neptune, hang on!
Neptune，抓緊！
Blake! I'm in position!
Blake，我已就位！
Freezer burn!
冰火二重天
Checkmate!
將軍！
Ladybug
瓢蟲對稱斬
Yang!
Yang！
Don't worry
別擔心
With each hit she gets stronger
她每挨一下都會變強
and she uses that energy to fight back!
然後用這些能量反擊！
That's what makes her special
這就是她的特點
Bumblebee!
大黃蜂攻擊！
We have to slow it down!
必須讓它減速！
And how do you propose we do that?
你準備讓我們怎麼做？
Iceflower!
用冰花！
Just got this thing cleaned..
我才剛弄乾淨..
Ladies..
女士們..
Ice Queen..
冰雪女王..
Hey!
你夠！
Always a pleasure
每次都很榮幸
Neo, if you would..
Neo，你也打個招呼..
So I guess he got a new henchman
看來他弄了個新幫手
Yeah, I guess she really made our plans..
是啊，她還真的把我們的計劃弄得..
fall apart..
支離破碎..
No, Just..no
別，快..停下
What？But you do it
哈？但你也玩梗啊
There's a time and a place for jokes
開玩笑要看時機與場合
Was this not it?
現在這樣不行？
No, it just..wasn't very good
不，只是..不太好
Well, at least I'm trying
哼，至少我有嘗試
Wait..
等等..
Where are Sun and Neptune?
Sun和Neptune在哪兒？
They're probably fine, right?
簡易干鍋 麵店
Probably
應該吧
BRB
BRB
This SUB is presented by Baidu RWBY Bar Creator: sbz_kid
本字幕由百度RWBY吧提供 片源/翻譯/時間軸/後期：sbz_kid